I never dreamed before
I'm gonna knock the door
into the world of perfect free
(You ain't no lonely!)
You're gonna say I'm lying
I'm gonna get the chance
I thought a chance is far from me
(You ain't no lonely!)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
You are the sun, you are the star
(To me, forever)
I was made to hit in America
(I was made to hit in America)
Yeah...Yeah...Okay. I'll leave
everything about the contract to you.
Yeah...
What? The band name
"Beck" is no good there?
Then you name something
works good in U.S.
Yeah. I'll send you the DAT
as soon as possible.
Okay. 'Bye...
Hey, Ryusuke! Are you here?
What?! An overseas debut?
So easily? I mean...we're lucky.
No, I don't think
we should expect too much.
True, it's the U.S.,
but this is a very obscure label.
Yeah...Um...Mr. Albin...
The guy with the name card, right?
But, I can feel the enthusiasm in him.
He says Beck is the best band
he's heard in Japan.
Hmm...
America! Blonde beauties.
I wonder if we'd fit in better overseas...
America?
"Live 17
'Three Days'"
Here you go.
Thank you very much!
Unusual for a customer be so thankful...
Yeah...I haven't seen a customer
so happy in a long time.
Yukio! You're too loud!
Oh...I'm sorry!
Let's see...Volume...volume...Okay.
Oh? Till morning?
Yeah. It's completely different
from a Gretsch so it's a lot of fun!
A Telecaster?
Mm-hmm...I even took
a day off my job for this.
I see...
-Be careful you don't lose your job!
-Uh-huh...
Oh! That girl!
-Oh...It is!
-Huh?!
Ooh...Ouch...
Are you all right?
I-I guess so...
You...Aren't you the girl
working at the donut shop?
Tanaka...kun?
"Health Room"
How did you know my name?
Well, you're always getting scolded.
Oh, is that why? How embarrassing!
Okay. I'm done.
It's nothing serious, but be
careful for two or three days.
All right.
The employees aren't treated
very well at that shop.
That's why the worker
turnover is so great.
Tanaka-kun...Can you play the guitar?
Huh? You can play, can't you?
No. Not at all.
I...This guitar case...
I saw it in the Light Music Club room.
Yeah...The club leader yelled at me,
so I quit after three days.
Your name?
Oh! I'm Hiromi Masuoka.
Hiromi Masuoka...Hiromi Masuoka...
Hiromi Masuoka...
Hiromi Masuoka, Hiromi Masuoka...
Wow...
Why, you're good, Tanaka-kun.
What's that song you just sang?
It's a song called Face by Beck.
I'm impressed, Tanaka-kun.
Thank you. This guitar seems to be fine.
-Shall I give you lessons, then?
-Yes. Thank you!
Thank you for letting me use
your White Falcon all this time.
Mm-hmm...Let me know anytime
you want to use it.
You can borrow it anytime.
All right.
Uh...hello...I'm ready anytime.
What about you, Momo-chan?
I see. Then, see you as usual
in front of the dog...Bye...
Momoko-sensei!
Actually, word got out that I once
worked for a week at a cabaret club
thanks to a former student.
It became a problem among the staff
when they found out I had kept it a secret.
It was such a shock.
I was really troubled over it.
I tried going to various seminars...
-And then...
-I became her confidant.
No one understands better than I do
about the entertainment business.
Yeah, better than anyone...
Ouch!
Our relationship is still platonic,
so don't go saying anything unnecessary.
Mm...
So long, Koyuki-kun!
Kenichi Saito, 44...Currently dashing
through the roads of his youth.
I haven't seen you
at work recently, Masuoka-san.
The truth is, I made a mistake
that was a big blow to the shop,
and so they fired me...
But I'm really excited
about the new club I joined!
Oh...
So long...
Grade 10-B, Hiromi Masuoka...
Huh? You know her?
Sure. I've checked her out.
Ohh...
When she was in intermediate school,
she had a good record.
Oh?
I wonder if she wouldn't
come to our live show...
I wonder...
Hiromi, why don't you take
a break? You must be thirsty.
-Here.
-Thanks!
Okay! I'll invite her later.
Huh?
"Belle Ame-First National Live House Tour"
"Expectations High for New Band"
Beck...eat it.
Hello? Hey, Mr. Albin...
Hey, how's our CD going?
What?!
Brother...It's because of your victory...
that I am now able to walk!
Huh...Don't be silly...
Brother...Brother!!
Thank you very much!
Hmm...
What are you doing, kid?!
I'm sorry!
...feel totally loose
This crazy, crazy world
You just have to Stage Dive or Die
Mind blower, a shower of sweat
Run towards a new world, my life
Those who seek it will be rewarded
Pass the hot shot
Keep on coming, come on!
Blow your mind
What are you doing, Koyuki?!
Boy, am I hungry.
Yeah...
Let's have some ramen noodles
before we head home.
Hmm...Good idea.
Ramen again?!
Yo!
Huh?
Sorry to keep you waiting.
Where's Ryusuke-kun?
Something came up so he gave me
the tickets and told me to go.
"'Three Days' Directed by Jim Walsh-
No.1 hit in U.S.!!"
Why are you always like this?!
What can I do? Our way
of living is too different.
Right. That's it, then.
Maybe...
I still love you.
Me, too.
Take care.
-The movie was a little hard to understand,
but the characters were so real
-It's been a while. How's life?
-The movie was a little hard to understand,
but the characters were so real
-I'm alive...
-that when the movie ended,
I felt a little sad leaving them.
-It's a tough world.
-That when the movie ended,
I felt a little sad leaving them.
-Yeah.
Jim Walsh...This director is a genius!
Yeah. It was interesting.
Why, I didn't get sleepy at all.
I hear this movie is such a hit that
Dying Breed's concert tour movie
is going to be released
simultaneously in the U.S. And Japan.
Oh? Their concert tour movie?
Hi!
Maho, I'm going to have dinner with Morita
and Eguchi-san, whom I'm playing with.
Are you free on Saturday?
That's nice, but I've got a Beck's live.
He says he's having
dinner with Eguchi-san!
Huh?!
Call me again the next time.
-What?! You're not gonna say you...
-Bye!
Now...Let's go and get something to eat.
Okay!
What? Really!
Yeah. They seem to be selling pretty well.
Our song...
Seems it's unusual for a Japanese band.
That president gets things done.
Uh...His name was Albin-san, was it?
What's wrong?
I should've signed
the contract for royalties.
What? You mean it doesn't matter
how many copies they sell?!
-So no matter how many
copies they sell...
-Ouch!
What...What? Aargh!
Spice!
Check, check, check, check...
Uh! Uh!
Blow your mind
Squeeze your sweat yeah
Squeeze your sweat
Large lips in the motion
Trying to keep blaming on
As I say reason I'm late on
Find you turning
Laughing and smiling
My ears are still ringing...
but it was really great.
Really? I'm glad.
Right, Saku?
Yeah, for real.
It was awesome!
And the crowd was huge!
Little by little we've been
getting bigger crowds.
Come again, Masuoka-san.
-I will!
-Hmph!
I hear Beck's playing
at the Marquee next.
No way...That's terrific!
They're really gaining in popularity.
Say, didn't that guy look
like Yoshito Morozumi?
No way...Really?
He wouldn't be in a place like this...
Hmph! They're nothing but
a little-known amateur band!
There was a message from the president.
They're going to print
more copies of our CD.
So our music is playing in America?
Yeah...
-Say...
-Huh?
Can you tell me the story?
Where did you get it?
I stole it.
You broke into cars?!
We had time on our hands,
so Eddy and I often did it.
And then we came upon that hot car.
What surprised us more was...
That's Lucille!
What? This car is no good, Eddy.
No, look! This is Sonny Boy Waters' guitar.
He's a blues guitarist.
Even Eric Clapton respects him.
He's a legend.
Sonny Boy?
Serial Number...8-3001...
Dude, that's it!
Come on! Let's go!
See, Sonny Boy and this guy were
fighting over this woman
called Lucille in a night club.
And the guy shot Sonny Boy
right on the stage.
You mean, during the play?
The guitar's been called Lucille
ever since then.
That's insane...
Okay. Let's get outta here. Come on.
Hey, Ray!
I kind of like this guitar.
What?
I'll be the legend after Sonny Boy.
-Huh?
And that's when I met up with Beck.
I found out later...
The car belonged to
someone really dangerous.
And now he's searching frantically
for Beck and Lucille.
"Director Jim Walsh's Newest Film-
Dying Breed's Road Tour Movie"
Hey! We have a group in. Your break is up.
Okay...I'll be right there!
Another minute
Feelin' so fine
You turn the freeze
into warm light
Had a premonition
I've been waitin' ever since
My world comin' down
It's got me spinnin' 'round
If you really wanna fly
you gotta let go
Simply the most
big sensation
(once you're here you won't go back)
She's really pretty
One-eyed vision
(lose the fear it don't come back)
Little sister showed me
Really took me for a ride
My world comin' down
(once you're here you won't go back)
(lose the fear it don't come back)
-I'm Atsushi.
-I'm Eriko.
-Together we are...
-The Chipped Teapot...Boing...
"Live 18 'Leon Sykes'"
-Together we are...
-The Chipped Teapot...Boing...
"Live 18 'Leon Sykes'"
Bonny Jump is doing a live show.
-Be sure to come...
...and watch.